<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For Parents on AskCher</title>
    <link>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/categories/for-parents/</link>
    <description>Recent content in For Parents on AskCher</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/categories/for-parents/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Primary School Class Sizes: Does it really matter?</title>
      <link>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/posts/small-class-sizes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/posts/small-class-sizes/</guid>
      <description>Small classes sizes are beneficial, yet almost impossible to achieve in Singapore schools. Learn how to accelerate learning even beyond the limitations of the classroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurturing Future-Ready Learners: The New Era of Learning</title>
      <link>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/posts/future-ready-learners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/posts/future-ready-learners/</guid>
      <description>Navigating primary school today means preparing your child for a world shaped by technology and evolving skills. This article explores how education is moving beyond traditional classrooms toward self-directed and holistic learning, focusing on crucial soft skills and emotional resilience. It provides practical tips for parents on how to be an active guide, from teaching children to handle failure to mastering AI as a tool, not a crutch. Ultimately, it’s about creating a strong parent-school partnership to nurture adaptable, creative, and future-ready learners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preparing your child for the PSLE</title>
      <link>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/posts/psle-final-tips-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/posts/psle-final-tips-2025/</guid>
      <description>As the PSLE approaches, get some essential guidance for the final weeks leading up to the PSLE, as recommended by a tutor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than Grades: Why Self-Discipline and Focus Are Your Child&#39;s Real Superpowers</title>
      <link>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/posts/building-discipline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/posts/building-discipline/</guid>
      <description>Is your child struggling to focus on homework? Discover five practical strategies from a Singapore tutor on how you can build a strong foundation of focus and self-control at home to set your child up for success in school and in life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Screens, Healthy Habits: Guiding Your Child&#39;s Digital Journey in Primary School</title>
      <link>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/posts/digital-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/posts/digital-habits/</guid>
      <description>Discover practical strategies and the latest guidelines to help you cultivate healthy digital habits and responsible screen use for your primary school child.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tips and Best Practices for Primary School Education for Your Child</title>
      <link>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/posts/primary-school-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/posts/primary-school-tips/</guid>
      <description>Navigating Singapore&amp;rsquo;s primary school system can feel overwhelming. This post offers parents practical, no-nonsense advice to help your child thrive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tuition Trap: Is More Always Better?</title>
      <link>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/posts/too-much-tuition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ask-cher-blog.vercel.app/posts/too-much-tuition/</guid>
      <description>Trying to figure out if your child needs more tuition? This post by a Singaporean tutor explains why adding more classes might not be the best solution. Discover how to get to the real root of their academic struggles and empower them to become a resilient, confident learner.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
